VOICE OVER: Raspberries placed on the top
of a glistening chocolate cake
An egg being broken into a mixing bowl.
An oven door being closed
then icing sugar dusted
onto fresh cream scones
Hashtag GBBO
This butter is not melting and it looks
like potato croquettes in like gravy
JAMES: Oh Rylan you've melted
hearts quicker than that
I have, that's a true statement
He gives a wink
James' flapjacks
have a definite wobble
Right, I wish I were dead
SANDI: Do you want a snog?
Noel's fake mouth falls off
James gives his flapjacks a prod then
shuts the freezer door in despair
James' cherry bakewell flapjacks
haven't been cut into pieces
and the runny topping
has been thrown on at the last minute
Uh can you tell us about
your flapjack please?
Started making it,
had a breakdown
bon appetit
James' deconstructed horn
Prue: Are you alright?
They've made scrambled egg
Prue: Oh right
which leaves in first place
this one
Michelle's thrilled
Rylan cowers as he holds his
bowl over his immaculate hair
James is less hesitant
That's confidence, isn't it?
I didn't even-
That wasn't hesitant there
ah ah is it doing it?
But would someone who
plays by the book do this?
He squirts meringue
into his mouth
Delicious
Oh. Instantly smushed one
James
One of Russell's meringues breaks
Rylan's Ibiza meringue scene
features piped waves
a miniature Rylan on a beach,
a shark's fin jutting out of the water
and a slightly dodgy looking rock
covered with melted chocolate
Paul: I actually think
it looks amazing
Prue: That guy looks exactly like you
it's just amazing
Bon appetit
[All laugh]